

1613 Stone Coal Rd Belington, West Virginia, 26250 chaseswick@gmail.com 304-591-2926

My name is Chase, and I am a graduate from West Virginia University with a Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering. I am a Full Stack Software Developer with experience in building full stack web applications. I have a lot of experience in Spring Boot/Angular from my time working at Revature, and some experience on personal projects using the .NET stack and React.

Professional Experience

Full Stack Software Developer Revature | March 2022 - October 2022

- Trained in all areas to learn how to create full stack web applications
- · Worked on projects using Spring Boot/Angular with AWS within an agile team using scrum methodology

Rater Telus International | February 2020 - Present

- Analyze AI training data to improve search engine quality.
- Utilize online tools to provide feedback on text, web pages, images, videos, and other media.
- Work under a strict time constraint to complete tasks efficiently.

Education

Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering West Virginia University at Morgantown | August 2015 - May 2022

Key Skills

- Java (5 years)
- Javascript (2 years)
- HTML/CSS (2 years)
- · React (1 year)
- Angular (1 year)
- C# (1 year)
- SQL (1 year)

Links

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/chase-swick-bb94ba233/
- Github: https://github.com/Swicky97

Projects

A Magic the Gathering TCG E-commerce website built with a focus on frontend development.

Tech Stack: React, JS, HTML, CSS

Link: https://mtg-outlet-react.herokuapp.com/